{
    "subject": "resource/Barry_Van_Dyke",
    "predicate": "property/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Georgia_(U.S._state)",
    "human_readable": "Barry Van Dyke was born in Georgia.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8822644948959351,
            "question": "Where was Barry Van Dyke born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5319570302963257,
            "question": "Who are some famous people born in Georgia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45284757018089294,
            "question": "What is Barry Van Dyke known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35546883940696716,
            "question": "Is Barry Van Dyke an actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3423630893230438,
            "question": "Does Barry Van Dyke have any famous relatives?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22095642983913422,
            "question": "Name some of Barry Van Dyke's notable film or television appearances."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21531392633914948,
            "question": "What state is Georgia located in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20891962945461273,
            "question": "What type of roles has Barry Van Dyke played in his career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18262548744678497,
            "question": "In what decades was Barry Van Dyke most active in the entertainment industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16155530512332916,
            "question": "Has Barry Van Dyke won any awards for his acting?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Barry Van Dyke was born in Georgia.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1203_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what decades was Barry Van Dyke most active in the entertainment industry?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1203_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of roles has Barry Van Dyke played in his career?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1203_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What state is Georgia located in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1203_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1203_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1203_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1203_125.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1203_134.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1203_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1203_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1203_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1203_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1203_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1203_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. According to multiple files (75.txt, 109.txt, 58.txt, and 31.txt), Barry Van Dyke was indeed born in Atlanta, Georgia, USA."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that Barry Van Dyke was born in Atlanta, Georgia. This supports the statement that Barry Van Dyke was born in Georgia."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}